crex24.com 2019-03-30

# Privacy Policy | CREX24

#### **General provisions**

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the "Policy") governs the collection, processing and use of personal information of users of the service CREX24 (hereinafter referred to as the "Service"). By using the Service, the Customer (hereinafter referred to as the "Customer") automatically agrees to the terms of this Policy.

This Policy can be modified at any time at the discretion of the Administration of the Service. The Customer must independently monitor the changes of the Policy on the CREX24 website at https://crex24.com (hereinafter referred to as the "Website"). The revised version of the Policy shall take effect immediately after it is published on the Website.

####  **Receiving and using information about Customers**

For the purpose of registering and gaining access to the services, the Customer shall complete a verification procedure and provide the Service with personal information (hereinafter referred to as "Personal Information"), including e-mail address and a photo of their identity document (passport).

For administrative purposes when running the Service, the following anonymized statistical data is collected on Users:

  * information about the browser and operating system;
  * IP address;
  * URL address;
  * other statistical data related to the use of the Website.

####  **Delete or amend Personal Information**

Customers should contact Customer Support team to modify the Personal Information provided.

The Service shall store the Customer's Personal information until the Customer's account is deleted. In order to delete the account, the Customer should contact the Customer Support team.

The Service may store Customer data for the fulfilment of legal obligations and dispute resolution.

####  **Disclosure of personal information**

The Customer's personal information may be disclosed to third parties, as required by law, only by court order, at the request of law enforcement or other government agencies.

####  **Cookie**

The Service uses cookies to improve the services it provides. Customers may disable cookies in browser settings but this cause the Service to function incorrectly.

####  **Links to third-party resources**

The Service may contain links to third-party websites. The Service will not be held responsible for the use of such links. The Customer should review the Privacy Policy of third-party websites independently.

####  **Protection of Personal Information**

The Service uses standard encryption and storage technology and makes every effort to protect Customers' Personal Data. However, none of the means of transferring and storing data over the Internet can guarantee complete data security.

####  **Contacts**

In the event of any issues related to this Policy, please contact the Customer Support Team of the Service.
